A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976, RG 3 FA094
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976; 3; 636.07 Cubic Feet 1659 containers - 1591 letter document boxes, 66 legal document boxes, 1 legal tall box, and 1 half-letter box.
  - Rockefeller Family, 1962-1976; 25; 79.83 Cubic Feet 205 letter document boxes, 4 legal document boxes and 1 half-letter box
    - David Rockefeller (and family), 3
      - Wing, William/DR Project - Harvard University (Box 1320, Folder 2)
      - Wing, William/DR Project - Notes (Box 1320, Folder 3)
      - Wing, William/DR Project - Interdenominational Committee for Religious Education on Released Time (Box 1320, Folder 4)
      - Wing, William/DR Project - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) (Box 1320, Folder 5)
      - Wing, William/DR Project - International House (Box 1321, Folder 1)
      - Wing, William/DR Project - Lincoln School (Box 1321, Folder 2)
      - Wing, William/DR Project - Morningside Heights (Box 1321, Folder 3)
      - Wing, William/DR Project - Museum of Modern Art (Box 1321, Folder 4)
      - Wing, William/DR Project - Near East Emergency Donations, Inc. (NEED) (Box 1321, Folder 5)
      - Wing, William/DR Project - Rockefeller University (Box 1322, Folder 1)
      - Wing, William/DR Project - Real Estate Ventures (Box 1322, Folder 2)
      - Wing, William/DR Project - Trilateral Commission (Box 1322, Folder 3)
      - Wing, William/DR Project - White House Fellows (Box 1322, Folder 4)
      - Wing, William/DR Project - Typescripts (Original) (Box 1323, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, Peggy (Box 1314, Folder 5, Box 1315, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, Peggy - Contributions (Box 1315, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller, Peggy - Maine Coast Heritage Trust (Box 1315, Folder 3-4)
      - Rockefeller, Peggy - Maine Coast Heritage Trust - Contributions (Box 1315, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, Peggy - Music Assistance Fund (Box 1316, Folder 1-2)
      - Rockefeller, Peggy - Property - Seal Harbor (Box 1316, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, Peggy - Property - Seal Harbor - Swan's Island (Box 1316, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, David Jr. (Box 1317, Folder 1-2)
      - Rockefeller, David Jr. - Investments - Real Paper (Box 1317, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, David Jr. - Trips (Box 1317, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, Margaret D. (Peggy) (Box 1408, Folder 4-5)
      - Rockefeller, Richard (Box 1449, Folder 1-3)
    - John D. Rockefeller (and family), 4
      - Rockefeller, John D. (Box 1323, Folder 2-3)
      - Rockefeller, Laura Spelman (Box 1323, Folder 4)
      - John D. Rockefeller's Birthplace (Box 1267, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller Family - Cousins (Box 1324, Folder 1-3)
        Restricted - Living Rockefeller family - Restricted for Life
      - The John D. Rockefeller Family Cemetery Corp. (Box 1324, Folder 4-5)
      - Rockefeller, John D. - Trust (Box 1324, Folder 6)
      - Rockefeller, John D. - Trust (Box 1324, Folder 6a)
      - Rockefeller, John D. - Trust - Margaret de Cuevas, 1937 (Box 1324, Folder 7)
    - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. (and family), 5
      - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. - Trusts (Box 1324, Folder 8)
        Restricted - LSR personal finances - Open in 2029
      - Rockefeller, John D. Jr. (Box 1325, Folder 1-2)
      - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. - Portrait (Box 1325, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. - Works of Art (Box 1325, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich (Box 1325, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, Martha Baird (Box 1325, Folder 6-7)
      - Rockefeller, Martha Baird - Personal Assistance Cases (Box 1325, Folder 8, Box 1326, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, Martha Baird - Personal Assistance Cases Memoranda (Box 1326, Folder 2-3)
      - Rockefeller, Martha Baird - Personal Assistance Cases Trust (Box 1326, Folder 4-7, Box 1329, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, Martha Baird - Estate (Box 1327, Folder 1-2, Box 1328)
      - Rockefeller, Martha Baird - Material re. her death (Box 1327, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, Martha Baird - Works of Art (Box 1327, Folder 4-5)
      - Rockefeller, Martha Baird - Memorial Service (Box 1329, Folder 2)
    - JDR 3rd Fund, 6
      - JDR 3rd Fund - A-I (Box 1329, Folder 3-4)
      - JDR 3rd Fund - J-Z (Box 1330, Folder 1-4)
      - Annual Reports (Box 1331, Folder 1-2)
      - Arts in Education (Box 1331, Folder 3-5)
      - Board of Trustees (Box 1332, Folder 1)
      - Contributions (Box 1332, Folder 2)
      - Meetings/Minutes (Box 1332, Folder 3-4, Box 1333, Folder 1-3, Box 1334, Folder 1)
      - Finances and Finance Committee (Box 1334, Folder 2-3)
      - Pagan Archaeological Center (Box 1334, Folder 4)
      - Public Affairs (Box 1334, Folder 5)
      - Young, Kenneth T. (Box 1334, Folder 6)
      - Youth Task Force (Box 1335, Folder 1-4)
    - John D. Rockefeller 3rd family, 7
      - Rockefeller, Blanchette (Box 1335, Folder 5-7, Box 1336, Folder 1-2)
      - Rockefeller, John D. IV, Jay (Box 1336, Folder 3-4)
      - Rockefeller, John D. IV, Jay - Speech at West Virginia Bankers Association, 1974 July 27 (Box 1336, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, John D. IV, Jay - Articles (Box 1337, Folder 1-2)
      - Rockefeller, John D. IV, Jay - Political Clippings (Box 1337, Folder 3-4)
      - Rockefeller, Sharon (Box 1338, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, John D. IV, Jay - West Virginia Wesleyan College (Box 1338, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller, John D. IV, Jay - Costa Smeralda, Sardinia (Box 1338, Folder 3-4)
      - Rockefeller, Sandra Ferry (Box 1451, Folder 1-6)
      - Spencer, Mr. and Mrs. John, Hope Rockefeller (Box 1472, Folder 8, Box 1473, Folder 1)
    - Laurance S. Rockefeller (and family), 8
      - Addresses - A-G (Box 1340, Folder 1-4)
      - Addresses - H-R (Box 1341, Folder 1-4)
      - Addresses - S-Z (Box 1342, Folder 1)
      - Addresses - Adirondack Mountain Club (Box 1342, Folder 2)
      - Addresses - American Society of Landscape Architects (Box 1342, Folder 3)
      - Addresses - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) (Box 1343, Folder 1-2)
      - Addresses - National Association of Counties, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1967 January 28 (Box 1343, Folder 3)
      - Addresses - Rockefeller, J.D. Jr. Memorial Parkway (Box 1343, Folder 4)
      - Addresses - Princeton Alumni Association, 1971 June 7 (Box 1344, Folder 1)
      - Addresses - Princeton Environmental Teach-in, 1970 April 21-22 (Box 1344, Folder 2)
      - Addresses - Speech material (Box 1344, Folder 3)
      - Addresses - U.S. Government-Joint House-Senate Colloquium on Environmental Policy (Box 1344, Folder 4, Box 1345, Folder 1)
      - Addresses - YMCA Dodge Medallion Award Dinner (Box 1345, Folder 2)
      - Articles - A-F (Box 1345, Folder 3)
      - Articles - A-N (Box 1346, Folder 1-3)
      - Articles - N-Z (Box 1347, Folder 1-3)
      - Articles - Associated Press, ORRRC, 1962 February 11 (Box 1347, Folder 4)
      - Articles - National Geographic Magazine, 1967 (Box 1347, Folder 5)
      - Articles - Articles by LSR (Box 1348, Folder 1)
      - Articles - General Electric Forum (Box 1348, Folder 2)
      - Articles - Life and Saturday Evening Post, 1961 December (Box 1348, Folder 3-4)
      - Articles - Meeman, Edward J. (Box 1348, Folder 5)
      - Articles - Readers Digest, 1972-1976 (Box 1349, Folder 1-4, Box 1350, Folder 1)
      - Articles - Readers Digest - A-Z, 1976 (Box 1350, Folder 2-3)
      - Awards (Box 1351, Folder 1)
      - Awards - A-Z (Box 1351, Folder 2-3)
      - Awards - A-G (Box 1351, Folder 4)
      - Awards - H-Z (Box 1352, Folder 1-3)
      - Awards - American Cancer Society (Box 1352, Folder 4)
      - Awards - Camp Fire Club of America (Box 1353, Folder 1)
      - Awards - Fifth Avenue Association (Box 1353, Folder 2)
      - Awards - Garden Club of America, Dallas, Texas, 1967 March 31 (Box 1353, Folder 3)
      - Awards - National Council of State Garden Clubs (Box 1353, Folder 4)
      - Awards - The Wings Club, 1977 (Box 1353, Folder 5)
      - Awards - Lotos Club (Box 1354, Folder 1)
      - Awards - NYU - C. Walter Nichols Award (Box 1354, Folder 2)
      - Awards - Riverside Church - Charles Evans Hughes Award (Box 1354, Folder 3)
      - Awards - Theodore Roosevelt Association (Box 1354, Folder 4)
      - Awards - YMCA of Greater NY - Dodge Medallion Award (Box 1355, Folder 1)
      - Biography (Box 1355, Folder 2-4)
      - Biography - A-Z (Box 1356, Folder 1)
      - Book proposed (Box 1356, Folder 2)
      - Book purchases (Box 1356, Folder 3-4)
      - Book (Box 1356, Folder 5)
      - Calendars 1959 (Box 1356, Folder 6)
      - Calendars 1960-1963 (Box 1357, Folder 1-4)
      - Calendars 1964-1967 (Box 1358, Folder 1-4)
      - Calendars 1968-1971 (Box 1359, Folder 1-4)
      - Calendars 1971-1974 (Box 1360, Folder 1-3)
      - Christmas (Box 1360, Folder 4)
      - Clippings (Box 1361, Folder 1-2)
      - Contributions (Box 1361, Folder 3-6, Box 1362, Folder 2-3)
      - LSR/MFR Matching gifts, 1960-1973 (Box 1362, Folder 1)
      - Debut - Laura, Marion, Lucy (Box 1363, Folder 1)
      - Dinners/Luncheons (Box 1362, Folder 4)
      - Dinner/Luncheons - King Olav V of Norway (Box 1362, Folder 5)
      - Estate (Box 1363, Folder 2)
        Restricted - Open in 2029.
      - Fallout shelters (Box 1363, Folder 3-5)
      - Finances (Box 1364, Folder 1-3)
      - Financial Consultants (Box 1364, Folder 4)
      - Capital Fund Reports, 1963-1971 (Box 1365, Folder 1)
      - Capital Fund - Statements (Box 1365, Folder 2)
      - Cudd & Co. (Box 1365, Folder 3-4, Box 1366, Folder 1-3)
      - Furnishings (Box 1367, Folder 1)
      - Garrison Development Corp. (Box 1367, Folder 2-4)
      - Garrison Development Corp. - Financial Statements (Box 1368, Folder 1)
      - Garrison Development Corp. - Financial - Loan Guaranty (Box 1368, Folder 2)
      - Gifts (Box 1368, Folder 3-4)
      - Invitations (Box 1369, Folder 1)
      - Invitations - A-Z (Box 1369, Folder 2)
      - Invitations to Speak - A-M (Box 1369, Folder 3-4)
      - Invitations to Speak - B-N (Box 1370, Folder 1-5)
      - Invitations to Speak - N-S (Box 1371, Folder 1-5)
      - Invitations to Speak - S-Z (Box 1372, Folder 1-3)
      - Jewelry (Box 1372, Folder 4-5)
      - Mail (Box 1372, Folder 6)
      - Letterbook (Box 1372, Folder 7)
      - Investments (Box 1373, Folder 1)
      - Legal (Box 1373, Folder 2)
      - Loans (Box 1373, Folder 3-6, Box 1374, Folder 1-2)
      - Operation (Box 1374, Folder 3)
      - Photographs (Box 1375, Folder 1)
      - Politics (Box 1375, Folder 2)
      - Property (Box 1375, Folder 3-4)
      - Property - Hawaii (Box 1375, Folder 5)
      - Personal (Box 1376, Folder 1)
      - Procedures committee (Box 1376, Folder 2)
      - Property - New York - 834 Fifth Ave. (Box 1376, Folder 3-5, Box 1377, Folder 1-4)
      - Property - Theodore Muller - Interior Decorator - LSR's Homes, 1966-1974 (Box 1378, Folder 1)
      - Property - New York - 235-41 East 46th St. Corp. (Box 1378, Folder 2)
      - Property - New York - Fishers Island (Box 1378, Folder 3)
      - Property - JY Ranch - General (Box 1378, Folder 4)
      - Property - JY Ranch - A-Z (Box 1379, Folder 1-3)
      - Property - JY Ranch - A-M (Box 1379, Folder 4)
      - Property - JY Ranch - N-Z (Box 1380, Folder 1)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Accounts (Box 1380, Folder 2)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Accounting - General, 1961-1965 (Box 1380, Folder 3-5, Box 1381, Folder 1-2)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Album (Box 1381, Folder 3)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Appraisals (Box 1381, Folder 4)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Boats (Box 1382, Folder 1)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Budget (Box 1382, Folder 2-3)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Construction, 1961-1964 (Box 1382, Folder 4-5)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Equipment Purchases and Requests (Box 1382, Folder 6-7)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Automobiles (Box 1383, Folder 1)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Fees (Gratuities at Ranch) (Box 1383, Folder 2)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Fish and Fishing (Box 1383, Folder 3)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Furnishings (Box 1383, Folder 4-5)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Grazing Lands (Rental of) (Box 1383, Folder 6)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Horse Purchase (Box 1384, Folder 1)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Insect Control (Box 1384, Folder 2)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Mathews, Red and Belle General Correspondence (Box 1384, Folder 3)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Memos (Box 1384, Folder 4)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Blueprints & Maps (Box 1385, Folder 2)
      - Property - JY Ranch - National Park Service - Lease (Box 1384, Folder 5-6, Box 1385, Folder 1)
      - Property - JY Ranch - National Park Service - Sale/Gift (Box 1385, Folder 3)
      - Property - JY Ranch - National Park Service - Transfer of Land (Box 1385, Folder 6)
      - Property - JY Ranch - New Cabin (Box 1385, Folder 4)
      - Property - JY Ranch - New Cabin - Prints - Plans (Box 1385, Folder 5)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Photographs (Box 1385, Folder 7)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Rockefeller, Laurance S. (Box 1385, Folder 8)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Visits - General Procedure (Box 1386, Folder 1)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Visits - General - A-Z (Box 1386, Folder 2)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Visits - General Correspondence (Box 1386, Folder 3)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Visits, 1967-1976 (Box 1386, Folder 4-8, Box 1387, Folder 1-5)
      - Property - Pocantico Hills (Box 1388, Folder 1-2)
      - Property - Pocantico Hills - Kent House and Grounds (Box 1388, Folder 3)
      - Property - Rockwood Hall (Box 1388, Folder 4-5)
      - Property - Rockwood Hall - General Correspondence (Box 1389, Folder 1)
      - Property - Rockwood Hall - A-Z (Box 1389, Folder 2-3)
      - Property - Rockwood Hall - Clippings (Box 1389, Folder 4)
      - Property - Rockwood Hall - International Business Machines Corp. (IBM) (Box 1389, Folder 5)
      - Property - Woodstock (Box 1390, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - A-L (Box 1390, Folder 2-4)
      - Property - Woodstock - M-Z (Box 1391, Folder 1-3)
      - Property - Woodstock - Housing (Box 1391, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock - Alloway House (Box 1392, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - Hollis Gale Property (Box 1392, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock - Industrial Site - Park (Box 1392, Folder 3-4)
      - Property - Woodstock - Mrs. Lyndon B. Johnson Visit, 1967 June 10-12 (Box 1392, Folder 5)
      - Property - Woodstock - Legal (Box 1392, Folder 6)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Contributions (Box 1392, Folder 7)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Finances (Box 1392, Folder 8)
      - Woodstock Foundation, Inc. (Box 1392, Folder 9)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Grants (Box 1392, Folder 10)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Minutes/Meetings (Box 1393, Folder 1-2)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Annual Meeting, 1970 (Box 1393, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Inn - A-Z (Box 1394, Folder 1-3)
      - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Inn - Barton Reports (Box 1394, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Inn - Clippings (Box 1395, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Inn - Finances (Box 1395, Folder 2-3)
      - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Inn - Low Income Housing (Box 1395, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Inn - Opening (Box 1396, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - The Mansion (Box 1408, Folder 1)
      - Property - Pocantico Hills - General Correspondence and Memos (Box 1396, Folder 2)
      - Radio/TV (Box 1396, Folder 3-4)
      - Real Estate - Larsen, Leslie H. (Box 1396, Folder 5)
      - Real Estate - 30 Rockefeller Plaza Associates & Co., 1959-1964 (Box 1397, Folder 1)
      - Real Estate - F.C. Feise Company (Box 1397, Folder 2)
      - Staff meetings, 1974-1976 (Box 1397, Folder 3)
      - Trips, 1948-1963 (Box 1398, Folder 1-7, Box 1399, Folder 1, Box 1397, Folder 4-10)
      - Trips - South America, 1966 March-April (Box 1399, Folder 2-4)
      - Trips, 1962-1975 (Box 1400, Folder 1)
      - Trips - South Pacific, 1972 (Box 1400, Folder 2-4)
      - Trips - South Pacific - Printed Material, 1972 (Box 1401, Folder 1-2)
      - Trips - Alaska (Box 1401, Folder 3)
      - Trips - Hawaii, Eastern Airlines, 1968 (Box 1647, Folder 5)
      - Selective Service - Naval Reserve, 1942-1947 (Box 1401, Folder 4)
      - Works of Art A-F (Box 1401, Folder 5)
      - Works of Art - A-P (Box 1405, Folder 1-3)
      - Works of Art - N-Z (Box 1406, Folder 1-2)
      - Works of Art - Printed Material (Box 1406, Folder 3)
      - Works of Art - Soldwedel, Frederic (Box 1406, Folder 4)
      - Works of Art - "Beaver Dick" Leigh (Box 1407, Folder 1)
      - Property - Trusts (Box 1402, Folder 1-2)
      - Trusts for Children (Box 1402, Folder 3-4, Box 1403, Folder 1-3, Box 1404, Folder 1-2)
      - Laura's Wedding (Box 1404, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, Larry (Box 1339, Folder 1-7, Box 1328, Folder 3-6)
        Restricted - Living Rockefeller family member.
      - Rockefeller, Mary French (Box 1407, Folder 2-3)
      - Rockefeller, Mary French - Addresses (Box 1407, Folder 4-5)
      - Rockefeller, Mary French - Property (Box 1407, Folder 6)
      - Rockefeller, Mary French - Billings Farm, Inc. (Box 1408, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller, Mary French - Thoughts and Meditations (Box 1408, Folder 3)
      - Waletzky, Dr. & Mrs. Jeremy P., Lucy Rockefeller Hamlin (Box 1473, Folder 6-7)
        Restricted - Living Rockefeller family members
      - Weber, Mr. & Mrs. Warren T., Marion F. Rockefeller (Box 1473, Folder 8, Box 1474, Folder 1-4)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller (and family), 9
      - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Box 1408, Folder 6)
      - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - A-E (Box 1409, Folder 1-5)
      - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - F-L (Box 1410, Folder 1-4)
      - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - M-R (Box 1411, Folder 1-4)
      - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - S-Z (Box 1412, Folder 1-4)
      - Addresses - A-F (Box 1412, Folder 5)
      - Addresses - G-Z (Box 1413, Folder 1-2)
      - Addresses - International European Movement (Box 1413, Folder 3, Box 1414, Folder 1)
      - Articles (Box 1414, Folder 2)
      - Articles - A-Z (Box 1414, Folder 3-4)
      - Autographs (Box 1415, Folder 1)
      - Automobiles (Box 1415, Folder 2)
      - Awards (Box 1415, Folder 3)
      - Biography (Box 1415, Folder 4)
      - Birthday, 1974 (Box 1416, Folder 1)
      - Birthday, 1975 (Box 1416, Folder 2)
      - Birthday, 1976 (Box 1416, Folder 3)
      - Boats (Box 1416, Folder 4-5)
      - Boats - North Sea Trawler (Box 1417, Folder 1)
      - Books (Box 1417, Folder 2)
      - Christmas Card List 1976, 1975-1976 (Box 1417, Folder 3)
      - Christmas Gifts 1976 (Box 1417, Folder 4)
      - Christmas Gifts Acknowledgments 1976 (Box 1417, Folder 5)
      - Christmas Gifts Received 1976 (Box 1417, Folder 6)
      - Christmas Card 1975 (Box 1417, Folder 7, Box 1418, Folder 1)
      - Christmas Card 1975 - A-Z (Box 1418, Folder 2)
      - Christmas Card List 1975 - Miscellaneous List (Box 1418, Folder 3)
      - Christmas Card List 1975 - IBEC (Box 1418, Folder 4)
      - Christmas Card List 1975 - Museum of Modern Art (Box 1418, Folder 5)
      - Christmas Card List 1975 - New York State (Box 1418, Folder 6)
      - Christmas Card List 1975 - Office (Box 1418, Folder 7)
      - Christmas Card List 1975 - Personal (Box 1418, Folder 8)
      - Christmas Card List 1975 - United States Government (Box 1418, Folder 9)
      - Christmas Card List 1975 - Venezuela (Box 1419, Folder 1)
      - Christmas Gifts 1975 (Box 1419, Folder 2)
      - Christmas Gifts Acknowledgement 1975 (Box 1419, Folder 3)
      - Christmas Gifts Received 1975 (Box 1419, Folder 4)
      - Christmas Card 1974 (Box 1419, Folder 5)
      - Christmas Card List 1974 (Box 1419, Folder 6)
      - Christmas Card List 1974 - Miscellaneous List (Box 1419, Folder 7)
      - Christmas Card List 1974 - IBEC (Box 1419, Folder 8)
      - Christmas Card List 1974 - New York State (Box 1419, Folder 9)
      - Christmas Card List 1974 - Office (Box 1419, Folder 10)
      - Christmas Card List 1974 - Personal (Box 1419, Folder 11)
      - Christmas Card List 1974 - United States Government (Box 1419, Folder 12)
      - Christmas Card List 1974 - Venezuela (Box 1420, Folder 1)
      - Christmas Gifts 1974 (Box 1420, Folder 2)
      - Christmas Gifts Acknowledgment 1974 (Box 1420, Folder 3)
      - Christmas Gifts Received 1974 (Box 1420, Folder 4)
      - Christmas Card 1973 (Box 1420, Folder 5)
      - Christmas Card List 1973 - Congressional (Box 1420, Folder 6)
      - Christmas Card List 1973 - Executive Chamber and 55th St. (Box 1420, Folder 7)
      - Christmas Card List 1973 - Governor's Club (Box 1420, Folder 8)
      - Christmas Card List 1973 - Museum of Modern Art and Museum of Primitive Art (Box 1420, Folder 9)
      - Christmas Card List 1973 - New York Legislature (Box 1420, Folder 10)
      - Christmas Card List 1973 - Office (Box 1420, Folder 11)
      - Christmas Card List 1973 - Personal (Box 1421, Folder 1)
      - Christmas Gifts 1973 (Box 1421, Folder 2)
      - Christmas Gifts 1973 - Acknowledgment (Box 1421, Folder 3)
      - Christmas Gifts Received 1973 (Box 1421, Folder 4)
      - Christmas Card List 1972 - General Correspondence (Box 1421, Folder 5)
      - Christmas Card List 1972 - Executive Chamber - 55th St. (Box 1421, Folder 6)
      - Christmas Card List 1972 - Governor's Club (Box 1422, Folder 1)
      - Christmas Card List 1972 - IBEC - Overseas & USA (Box 1422, Folder 2)
      - Christmas Card List 1972 - Museum of Modern Art and Museum of Primitive Art (Box 1422, Folder 3)
      - Christmas Card List 1972 - NARFARMS (Box 1422, Folder 4)
      - Christmas Card List 1972 - New York State Delegation, County Chair and County Vice-Chair (Box 1422, Folder 5)
      - Christmas Card List 1972 - New York State Legislature (Box 1422, Folder 6)
      - Christmas Card List 1972 - Office (Box 1422, Folder 7)
      - Christmas Card List 1972 - Personal (Box 1422, Folder 8)
      - Christmas Card List 1972 - Rockefeller Center and Music Hall (Box 1422, Folder 9)
      - Christmas Gift List 1972 (Box 1422, Folder 10)
      - Christmas 1972 - Gifts Received (Box 1423, Folder 1)
      - Dinners/Luncheons (Box 1423, Folder 2-3)
      - Dinners/Luncheons - Echeverria Alvare, Luis, 1972 June 17 (Box 1423, Folder 4)
      - Dinners/Luncheons - State Dinner at Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1973 May 11 (Box 1423, Folder 5)
      - Dinners/Luncheons - Rainbow Room Lists, 1973 May 10 (Box 1424, Folder 1)
      - Dinners/Luncheons - Republican Governors Association Luncheon, 1973 May 11 (Box 1424, Folder 2)
      - Dinners/Luncheons (Box 1424, Folder 3)
      - Dinners/Luncheons - Kissinger, Mr. and Mrs. Henry (Box 1424, Folder 4-6)
      - Dyslexia (Box 1425, Folder 1)
      - Films (Box 1425, Folder 2)
      - Finances (Box 1425, Folder 3)
      - Finances - Investments (Box 1425, Folder 4)
      - Furnishings (Box 1425, Folder 5)
      - Gifts (Box 1425, Folder 6, Box 1426, Folder 1)
      - Gifts - Steuben Glass (Box 1426, Folder 2)
      - Giving Program (Box 1426, Folder 3)
      - Hauser (Box 1426, Folder 4)
      - Invitations - A-B (Box 1426, Folder 5)
      - Invitations - C-S (Box 1427, Folder 1-5)
      - Invitations - T-Z (Box 1428, Folder 1)
      - Invitations to Speak - A-C (Box 1428, Folder 2-4)
      - Invitations to Speak - C-K (Box 1429, Folder 1-5)
      - Invitations to Speak - L-P (Box 1430, Folder 1-4)
      - Invitations to Speak - Q-Z (Box 1431, Folder 1-3)
      - Jewelry (Box 1432, Folder 1-2)
      - Kissinger, Henry A. (Box 1432, Folder 3)
      - Memos (Box 1432, Folder 4)
      - Monthly Calendars (Box 1432, Folder 5)
      - Photos - A-D (Box 1432, Folder 6)
      - Photos - E-Z (Box 1433, Folder 1-2)
      - Printed Material (Box 1433, Folder 3)